<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Remote Newbie</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Remote Newbie</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Wondering if remote work is right for you? Find out.</title>
      <link>/post/is-remote-work-right-for-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/is-remote-work-right-for-you/</guid>
      <description>Remote work is becoming more of a norm.
It is being adopted by a wide array of industries for tons of different reasons. Some companies do it because it is cheaper, opens up their talent pool, increases productivity and opens up work hours, so they can be up and running 24/7. The part of this idea that goes less spoken about, is if it’s right for the employee? Specifically, is it right for you?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dear founders, here&#39;s how to handle the surge of remote work</title>
      <link>/post/founders-here-is-how-to-handle-the-surge-of-remote-work.md/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/founders-here-is-how-to-handle-the-surge-of-remote-work.md/</guid>
      <description>A letter to founders and managers,
If you’re a startup founder or you’re a hiring manager whose company has held a physical office with no remote employees, it’s sorta time for you to think about why this is. As the wave of millennials starts breaking and changing the workforce (for the better) there are going to major changes in the way on-boarding, job descriptions, inclusion, communications and more start to evolve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is remote work? And what you should know about it in 2019</title>
      <link>/post/what-is-remote-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/what-is-remote-work/</guid>
      <description>You may know of remote work in a few different ways, let’s cover them.
Telecommute or telecommuting  In the 1990s, this was the term used and brought to the media by way of pop culture. During this time mottos around telecommuting started to emerge as well, for example, “Work is something you do, not something you travel to.”  Digital nomad  Someone who works from their computer and re-locates every so often to travel, explore and run their business from literally anywhere in the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>3 tips for onboarding remote employees</title>
      <link>/post/3-tips-for-onboarding-remote-employees-in-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/3-tips-for-onboarding-remote-employees-in-2019/</guid>
      <description>Okay, so not only is it difficult to hire remote employees but it’s even harder to onboard them. Ideally, if your company can afford it it’s substantially easier to have an offsite to onboard the new hire in person but that’s not super realistic and never expected.
So, let’s talk about the alternative way to onboard a remote employee - asynchronously.
Set them up with essentials before their start date This one is big.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to deal with loneliness as a remote worker?</title>
      <link>/post/how-to-deal-with-loneliness-as-a-remote-worker-maker-founder/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/how-to-deal-with-loneliness-as-a-remote-worker-maker-founder/</guid>
      <description>Ever since I&amp;rsquo;ve started to work remote I&amp;rsquo;ve felt loneliness almost consistently.
It&amp;rsquo;s normal to feel this way and if you&amp;rsquo;re feeling this way right now, please know that you&amp;rsquo;re not alone.
Remote work can be isolating. It&amp;rsquo;s true. Everyone knows it but we find creative ways to overcome it. It does require a bit of extra effort so be prepared! Unfortunately, we aren&amp;rsquo;t in an office environment where being around other humans for 8 hours a day is a given.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Find remote engineering roles today</title>
      <link>/post/find-remote-engineering-roles-today./</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/find-remote-engineering-roles-today./</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ll be covering 2 big topics to help you find and land your next Remote Engineering role. The first is understanding how to best showcase that you&amp;rsquo;re open and ready to work in a remote work environment. Secondly, I&amp;rsquo;ll show you a few sites that have truly worked for friends in the past to find and at least get an interview for a remote role.
Building and starting to showcase your remote experience Here are few ways to spin remote work experience and showcase it if you&amp;rsquo;re applying for a job that requires remote experience:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>